(Bernadette:)So, what should we talk about?
(Howard:)Well, we could always learn more...
(Howard:)...about why people who believe
in psychics are idiots. Leonard?
(Penny:)We don't need
to talk about that anymore.
(Penny:)Leonard covered it pretty well
in the car.
(Leonard:)I'm sorry, but facts are facts.
(Penny:)Right, and if you can't understand it,
it's not a fact.
(Leonard:)No, if it's not a fact, it's not a fact.
(Penny:)-Oh, got it. Thank you for educating me.
-Oh, you're welcome.
(Leonard:)-How's your fish?
-Amazing.
(Penny:)-Would you like to try some?
-Yeah, sure.
(Penny:)Well, the fact is you can't.
(Leonard:)Howard, Bernadette,
you're both scientists.
(Leonard:)Help me out here.
Wanna jump in the middle
of another couple's argument?
(Bernadette:)-No, thank you.
-Sorry.
(Leonard:)Maybe we should just stop talking
about this.